This music video contains flashing colors
Viewer discretion is advised
このミュージックビデオには明るく点滅する色があります
気を付けてください
ファン翻訳 (okiyomi 沖詠)
Did it really happen
本当に起こったの
Or were they pieces thrown around
それとも散らばった欠片なのか
The past is all built on lies
過去は全部嘘から築かれている
Where one word could break it down
たった一言で壊れてしまう
Sorting recollections
記憶を整理して
Scanning for patterns to compare
比較できるパターンに目を走らせて
But nothing comes up to mind
でも何も思い浮かばない
In the fragments that I can't repair
直せない破片の中に
'Cause the sweetness on your face
だから君の顔の甘さ
And the tenderness of your warm embrace
と君の温かい抱擁の優しさ
Somehow they left a bitter taste
何故か苦い味を残した
There's nothing to trace
手繰るものは何もない
Painful times, they were all erased
つらい時、全部消されたのに
And yet my body's screaming
僕の体が叫んでいる
"Don't make the same mistake"
「同じ間違いをしないで」
Can I go ahead and surrender
降参してもいいのかな
To the visions that I just can't remember
どうしても思い出せない幻想に
Merging all of these memories
この記憶を全部混ぜ合わせて
To a blend of anomalies
異常の塊に
Reveal all the trauma I suffered
僕の受けたトラウマを全部明かして
I'll relive it all to be born much stronger
もっと強く生まれ変わるために、すべてを思い出すんだ
Then there's no way someone else can repeat
誰も同じ轍を踏まないように
What you did to me
あなたが僕にしたこと
"Did that really happen?"
「本当に起こったの？」
Thoughts into voices now reshaped
想いを声に、形を変えて
I wished for recovery
回復を求めたのに
But was given no escape
逃げ場は与えられなかった
Once, merely a single touch
前に、ただ一度触れたけど
Now, a swarm to undertake
今、大群に襲われる
It's surely too late for me
きっともう手遅れだ
'Cause my limit is going to break
僕の限界が破れそうになっている
Now, the sweetness on your face
さ、君の顔の甘さ
And the tenderness of your warm embrace
と君の温かい抱擁の優しさ
Somehow they left a bitter taste
何故か苦い味を残した
Oh, the memories stay
あ、この記憶は残る
Painful times are put on replay
苦しい時が再現されても
And still, my body's screaming
僕の体はまだ叫んでいる
"Don't make the same mistakes"
「同じ間違いをしないで」
Now I see through all your endeavours
あなたの仕業は全部見破れるぞ
And the sinful scars that I'll hold forever
この罪深い傷跡は永遠に負うだろう
Tainting all of these melodies
このメロディーをすべて汚している
Full of mixed-up apologies
混沌の申し訳だらけ
Was there any chance for me to run
逃げる機会はあったのだろうか
Was there something different that I could've done
何か違うやり方があったのだろうか
I'm left with a mangled mind that repeats
繰り返される、ぐちゃぐちゃな心が残っている
What you did to me
あなたが僕にしたこと
There was a reason they were thrown away
捨てられたのには理由があったよ
Why they were locked behind from my display
僕のディスプレイから閉じ込められた理由
And now my memory's in disarray
そして今、僕の記憶は混乱している
It forced a reinstall
再インストールを余儀なくされた
Remember to forget them all
すべてを忘れること、忘れないで
Can I go ahead and surrender
降参してもいいのかな
To the visions that I just can't remember
どうしても思い出せない幻想に
Merging all of these memories
この記憶を全部混ぜ合わせて
To a blend of anomalies
異常の塊に
Reveal all the trauma I suffered
僕の受けたトラウマを全部明かして
I'll relive it all, to be born much stronger
もっと強く生まれ変わるために、すべてを思い出すんだ
Then there's no way someone else can repeat
それで誰も同じ轍を踏まないように
What you did to me
あなたが僕にしたこと
Thank you for your support!
応援してくれてありがとう！
Did it really happen
本当に起こったの
Or were they pieces thrown around
それとも散らばった欠片なのか
The past is all built on lies
過去は全部嘘に築かれている
Where one word could break it down
たった一言で壊れてしまう